https://www.suppliesforhotels.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Supplies For Hotels
Skip to content
Toll Free: 1-682-444-5870
Shopping CartMy Account Remember MeRegisterCart
Search for:
HomeBathroom Bath AmenitiesBath RobesBath TowelsShower Curtain HooksShower Curtain RodsShower CurtainsBedding Bed LinensBedspreads & CoverletsBlanketsComforters & Duvet InsertsCustom BedspreadsCustom Quote FormDuvet CoversMattress PadsPillowsPillow ProtectorsTowels Bath TowelsKitchen TowelsPool TowelsOutdoor Lounge Chair CoversContact Customer ServiceRequest A QuoteJoin Our Newsletter
Search for:
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyBrett Stallings2017-02-22T08:31:30+00:00
Privacy Policy(Last Update: Nov 2016)
Information we gather
Humdinger Supply does not gather any information from you or your computer. We do not share ANY info with any of our vendors or partners. Your transaction is secured via a secure connection on a secure server. No information is passed openly or stored by our system. Thank you for shopping with Humdinger Supply. If you have any questions please email us at info@suppliesforhotels.com
How we use the information we gather
We use the information we collect at the time of purchase to process your order only. The information is not stored or used in any other way.
The people that are given access to this information
Your personal information is accessible by the store owner or assistant only. Humdinger Supply is a family business and we process each order by hand.
The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information
To safeguard your personal information, we have a SSL certificate installed on our secure server via GoDaddy.com all of your information is 100% secure and safely transmitted to the credit card processor.
Our use of cookies
Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.
Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.
Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.
Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
6688 Nolensville Rd.
© Copyright SuppliesforHotels.com 1996 -  All Rights Reserved  |   Website Design by Stallings Design Co.
COVID-19 UPDATE: Orders are currently delayed due to supply chain issues.
Please call 1-682-444-5870 to place your order.
